eudict.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy policy

EUdict take your privacy concerns seriously. We do not collect any personal information from users browsing this website. We use so-called LocalStorage to remember settings in your browser (language pair, your last searches, site language, speech language etc.).  
Although we took all the preventive measures to make this site safe, we are not responsible for any damage or loss related to use of the content found on this website. We cannot be held responsible if some offensive words from the search cloud end up indexed by the search engines. If you have received e-mail message that appears to be sent from eudict.com, please be assured that message is not sent from our server (email services are disabled) and sender have concealed his real email address. In web browsers supporting speech input (Google Chrome, Chromium) recorded word is transferred to Google servers.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. EUdict uses analytic software to collect data about web browsers and computers but this information contains no personal information about any visitor to our site; that is, no names, addresses, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and the like.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Would you like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies?  

  * [Exponential](http://exponential.com/privacy/) (Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collects and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time. For more details including access requests and complaints, review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com. Exponential uses ANON_ID (persistent tracking cookie), by domain tribalfusion.com. The anonymous hashed id in the cookie links the web user's browser to a profile which contains the behaviours the user has displayed. This is stored for 3 months.)

To opt-out from many sites you can try this [tool](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). 

#### How to control cookies

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see  [cookiesandyou.com](https://cookiesandyou.com/). You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.

EUdict reserves the right to change these terms of use and use of the web site at any time and shall not be liable for any possible consequences resulting from those changes. The mentioned changes take effect on publication on this web site.
